let coda_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_03_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_05_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_06_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_06_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_07_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_07_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_08_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_08_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_09_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_11_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_15_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_21_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AAB_AAP_1_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '8', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AAB_AAP_1_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_03_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_03_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_05_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_05_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_07_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_07_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_09_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_09_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_10_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_10_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_11_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_11_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_13_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_13_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_17_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_17_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_23_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_23_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'AHB_AHP_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/AHB_AHP_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '2', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_04_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_04_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_05_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_05_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_06_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_06_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_07_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_07_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_09_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_09_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_22_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_22_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'IHB_IHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '7', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/IHB_IHP_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_02_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '3', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_02_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_03_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_03_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_04_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_04_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_05_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_05_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_06_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_06_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_08_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_08_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_11_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_11_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_15_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_15_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_21_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_21_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_coda', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'coda_syllable', audio: 'UHB_UHP_5_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/coda_syllables/UHB_UHP_5_30_10.wav' }}]